

About me

Customer Support Executive

Key Skills

Excel Report Preparation

Excel Powerpoint

Outlook Configuration

Career Timeline

2022 - PresentZeon Electric Private Limited

2021 - 2022
 Lakshmi Stores UK

2017 - 2018 Integra Global Solutions

2016 - 2017 Tia Educational Institutions-Coimbatore June 2016- July 2017

2014 - 2015
Dynosus Solutions- Coimbatore Aug
2014- Nov 2015

Personal Details

Date of Birth **22-Apr-1994**

Gender **Female**

Address

83, 6th street, north vinayagapuram,saravnamaptti

Mahalakshmi

Team Lead customer support,

□ 9025502216

Profile Summary

Customer Care Executive with 3+ years of experience preparing flawless presentations, assembling facility reports, and maintaining the utmost confidentiality. A career in the related fields of which will enable me to exhibit my technical skill and apply my knowledge to add value to the organization and the environment.

Education

B.Sc

Sri Ramakrishna College of Arts & Science for Women, Coimbatore

2014 Full Time

Technical Skills

✓ Inventory Management

✓ Quality Control

✓ Customer Handling

Work Experience

City Coimabtore

Country **India**

Marital Status

Married

Team Lead customer support, Zeon Electric Private Limited

Nature of work

??? Inbound call handling

??? Anyone travelling more than 500 kilometres will be sent a map route.

??? Consolidate sheet preparation on a regular basis ??? Handling outlook email and customer service ??? Creating RFID tags for customer invoices and providing tracking information

??? Collect client comments on a daily basis as a TL on online chat.

??? Receiving customer feedback as a team with Freshdesk CRM CRM works experience ??? Create tickets on Freshdesk by each agent's name

??? NUMOCITY Interface CRM Edit Details??? Using Freshdesk CRM to handle marketing calls.Team Management

??? Managed operations efficiently and effectively, verifying customers received exceptional service. ??? Monitored team performance, providing suggestions for improvement and training programmes to increase team efficiency ??? Resolved complex customer enquiries, disputes and complaints.

??? Served as customer service team lead, enforcing company policies, answering co-workers' questions and training new staff.

??? Closely monitored team performance by conducting observations and tracking key metrics, identifying and managing underachievers appropriately.

2022 - Present

2021 - 2022

Team Lead- Customer Support Executive Lakshmi Stores UK

??? Plan and coordinate meetings, appointments, and travel for supervisors and managers.

??? During a period of corporate expansion, I trained three team assistants to ensure attention to detail and adherence to company policy.

??? Manage customer reports for members of the department team.

??? Typed communications, draughts, memoranda, and emails, as well as three weekly reports ??? Handling UK customer inquiries via email and

live chat during UK business hours
??? Customers will inquire about their order status
and product details, as well as track the DHL and

DPD courier status.

??? Create a Zoho desk ticket for any difficulties with the products the customer received and resolve it within 24 hours.

??? It is necessary to compile and organise an invoice.

??? Monitored operations to ensure employees followed relevant procedures and worked towards defined Key Performance Indicator (KPI) targets. ??? Maintained excellent employee relationships by cultivating supportive, positive and helpful working environment.

??? Planned employee workloads and delegated tasks strategically to meet seasonal fluctuations in demand.

??? Oversaw stock control to maintain sufficient inventory levels and minimise waste.

Tools

??? Zoho desk, Zoho mail, Zoho sales IQ, Zoho Inventory, and Zoho CRM were all used.

Customer Support Executive Integra Global Solutions

??? Handling consumer inquiries via email and live chat in US shifts

??? Working for Teechip and Teepro Client Companies

??? Complete the daily goal of 180 new and history emails

??? Resolved customer queries promptly using deescalation techniques.

??? Consistently exceeded productivity targets month-on-month through efficient customer service.

??? Provided customers with follow-up emails and other documentation as needed to promote customer support excellence.

2017 - 2018

2016 - 2017

Senior Trainer Learning and Development Tia Educational Institutions- Coimbatore June 2016- July 2017

??? Weekly meetings were recorded, transcribed, and distributed.

??? Answered up to 20 phone calls per day, taking thorough messages.

??? Scheduled appointments and ensuredexecutives arrived on time for client meetings.??? Created successful training courses based onevaluation of student needs.

??? Reduced process gaps by effectively training new hires on best practices and protocols.??? Provided additional materials to enhance training.

Customer Support Executive,

Dynosus Solutions- Coimbatore Aug 2014-Nov 2015

??? Handling customer queries via email in US shifts ??? Based on customer satisfaction will get star reward

??? Ensured customer service stayed excellent, attentive and helpful by proactively going the extra mile to assist customer needs.

??? Provided exceptionally high levels of customer service via live chat, email, phone and social media. ??? Built and maintained excellent relationships with customers, promoting high levels of customer retention.

2014 - 2015